Same amount of days
Same batch of frogs
Why are Lewes' frogs
growing so well
While mine are so skinny
Are you slacking off
I am not slacking off
Lewes is feeding them
His own secret feed
Our farm uses
Ordinary feed on the market
How can we compete
Secret feed
These frogs are at a critical
fattening stage
We need to add more
maggot powder
With enough protein
They will build thick fat
The season is changing lately
Big temperature difference
between day and night
Frogs easily get sick
We should add some
herbal medicine
To boost their immunity
Yeah this ratio is perfect
The herbal smell isn't too strong
So they won't refuse it
B-boss
We are out of feed
I will mix the feed
Go inside